A Guide to the Records of the Virginia Secretary of Public Safety, 1990; 1992; 1996; 1998-2010 (bulk 2002-2009)
Library of Virginia
- Series II. Correspondence and Supporting Documentation - Office of the Secretary, 1990; 1992; 1998-2009., Extent: 19.4 cubic feet (22 boxes). (Box 12-30)
  - Series II. Correspondence and Supporting Documentation - Office of the Secretary, Subseries B. Subject Files, 1990; 1992; 2001-2009., Extent: 9.05 cu. ft. (boxes 15-22c)
    - Homeland Security Grant Process, 2006. (Box 17, Folder 34)
    - Homeland Security Issues, 2006-2008. (Box 17, Folder 35)
    - Homeland Security Issues, 2004-2006. (Box 17, Folder 36)
    - Homeland Security Issues, 2002-2004. (Box 17, Folder 37)
    - The Office of Justice Programs' Implementation of the Hometown Heroes Survivors Benefits Act of 2003, March 2008. (Box 17, Folder 38)
    - HOV Lanes (Northern Virginia), 2005. (Box 18, Folder 1)
    - Hurricane Season Briefing, 2007. (Box 18, Folder 2)
    - ICJIS Charge Standardization Project, 2003-2004. (Box 18, Folder 3)
    - Immigration Task Force, 2004-2007. (Box 18, Folder 4)
    - Inauguration Planning, 25 November 2008. (Box 22b, Folder 1)
    - Presidential Inauguration Cost Reimbursement, 2009. (Box 18, Folder 5)
    - Incarcerated Juveniles/Parents, 2005. (Box 18, Folder 6)
    - Indigent Defense Reform, 2007. (Box 18, Folder 7)
    - Indigent Defense Task Force, 2004. (Box 18, Folder 8)
    - Information Requests from Public Safety Agencies, 2006. (Box 18, Folder 9)
    - Information Technology, 2002-2003. (Box 18, Folder 10)
    - Information Technology Monitoring and Review, 2002. (Box 18, Folder 11)
    - Inmate Telephone System (MCI/WorldCom), 2002-2004. (Box 18, Folder 12)
    - Inmate Telephone System (MCI/WorldCom), 2002-2004. (Box 18, Folder 13)
    - Innovations Awards Program, 2004. (Box 18, Folder 14)
    - Innovations Awards Program, 2003-2004. (Box 18, Folder 15)
    - Integrated Justice Program (IJP), 2005. (Box 18, Folder 16)
    - Integrated Justice Program Change Standardization, 2005. (Box 18, Folder 17)
    - Interagency Anti-Gang Workgroup, 2002-2005. (Box 18, Folder 18)
    - Interoperability, 2005; 2007. (Box 18, Folder 19)
    - Interoperability Grant, 2005. (Box 18, Folder 20)
    - Interoperability Strategic Plans, 2006-2007. (Box 22b, Folder 2)
    - Feasibility Study for Deploying Interoperability Channels, Executive Summary, 27 September 2007. (Box 22b, Folder 3)
    - Virginia Interoperability Baseline Assessment Report-Final, 27 September 2007. (Box 22b, Folder 4)
    - Virginia Statewide Interoperability Executive Committee meeting, 11 July 2008. (Box 22b, Folder 5)
    - Jail Contract Bed Program, 2004. (Box 18, Folder 21)
    - Jail Diversion Pilot Program, 2003. (Box 18, Folder 22)
    - Jamestown 400, 2007. (Box 18, Folder 23)
    - JLARC, 2002-2003. (Box 18, Folder 24)
    - Hurricane Katrina, 2005-2006. (Box 18, Folder 25)
    - Hurricane Katrina, 2005. (Box 18, Folder 26)
    - Post Katrina/Rita Evaluations, 2006. (Box 18, Folder 27)
    - Law Enforcement Officers' Memorial Service, 2007. (Box 18, Folder 28)
    - Legislation, 2002-2007. (Box 18, Folder 29)
    - Legislation (2007 Session), 2006. (Box 18, Folder 30)
    - License Plate Production, 2003. (Box 18, Folder 31)
    - Line-of-Duty Deaths, 2004-2006. (Box 18, Folder 32)
    - M/A-COM, 2002-2003. (Box 18, Folder 33)
    - Medal of Valor Award, 2002-2004. (Box 18, Folder 34)
    - Medal of Valor Award, 2005-2007. (Box 18, Folder 35)
    - Medical Care (DOC/ACLU), 2003. (Box 18, Folder 36)
    - Medical Clemency, 2002-2005. (Box 19, Folder 1)
    - Mental Health, 2008. (Box 19, Folder 2)
    - Methamphetamine, 2005. (Box 19, Folder 3)
    - Methamphetamine, 2006. (Box 19, Folder 4)
    - Methamphetamine Announcement, 2005. (Box 19, Folder 4)
    - Mothers Against Drunk Driving (MADD), 2004. (Box 19, Folder 5)
    - NAACP, 2002-2003. (Box 19, Folder 6)
    - National Alcohol Beverage Control Association (NABCA), Research Information Kit, Promoting Social Responsibility and Generating Revenue, September 2006. (Box 19, Folder 7)
    - National Capitol Region Meetings, 2005. (Box 19, Folder 8)
    - National Capital Region Homeland Security Strategic Plan for 2007-2009, August 2006. (Box 22b, Folder 6)
    - National Governors Association, 2003. (Box 19, Folder 9)
    - National Governors Association, 2003-2004. (Box 19, Folder 10)
    - National Incident Management System (NIMS), 2006-2007. (Box 19, Folder 11)
    - Naval Coastal Warfare Squadron Four Commissioning Ceremony, 2006. (Box 19, Folder 12)
    - Noble Resolve 07-1 (United States Joint Forces Command), 6 June 2007. (Box 22b, Folder 7)
    - Offender Management System, 2004. (Box 19, Folder 13)
    - Offender Population Forecasting Policy Advisory Committee, 2007. (Box 19, Folder 14)
    - Offender Population Forecasts, Report on the, 2006. (Box 19, Folder 15)
    - OxyContin Drug Information, 2002, 2005. (Box 19, Folder 16)
    - Pandemic, 2005. (Box 19, Folder 17)
    - Parole Board, 2005. (Box 19, Folder 18)
    - Parole Board Issues, 2002. (Box 19, Folder 19)
    - Policy Works/GOSAP, 2002. (Box 19, Folder 20)
    - Prescription Drugs/Medical Supplies (340B), 2003-2004. (Box 19, Folder 21)
    - Primary Seat Belt Law, 2003. (Box 19, Folder 22)
    - Printing Contract (VCE), 2004. (Box 19, Folder 23)
    - Prison Visits, 2006. (Box 19, Folder 24)
    - Prisoner Re-Entry Issues, 2007. (Box 19, Folder 25)
    - Problem People, 2002-2006. (Box 19, Folder 26)
    - Procurement Reports, 2002-2006. (Box 19, Folder 27)
    - Productivity Investment Fund, October 2007. (Box 22b, Folder 8)
    - Professional Association State Contacts, 2007. (Box 19, Folder 28)
    - Protect and Respect Interim Evaluation, 2006. (Box 19, Folder 29)
    - PROTECT Virginia, 2002. (Box 19, Folder 30)
    - Public Safety Policy Advisory Committee, 2004. (Box 19, Folder 31)
    - Public Safety Policy Advisory Committee, 2006. (Box 19, Folder 32)
    - Public Safety Agency Head Meetings, 2002 January-March. (Box 19, Folder 33)
    - Public Safety Agency Head Meetings, 2002 May-December. (Box 19, Folder 34)
    - Public Safety Agency Head Meetings, 2003 January-August. (Box 19, Folder 35)
    - Public Safety Agency Head Meetings, 2003 October-December. (Box 19, Folder 36)
    - Public Safety Agency Head Meetings, 2004 January-February. (Box 19, Folder 37)
    - Public Safety Agency Head Meetings, 2004 August-October. (Box 20, Folder 1)
    - Public Safety Agency Head Meetings, 2005. (Box 20, Folder 2)
    - Public Safety Agency Head Meetings, 2006. (Box 20, Folder 3)
    - Public Safety Agency Head Meetings, 2007 March. (Box 20, Folder 4)
    - Public Safety Agency Head Meetings, 2007 October-December. (Box 20, Folder 5)
    - Public Safety Agency Head Meetings, 2008. (Box 20, Folder 6)
    - Public Safety Board Protocol Meeting, 2007. (Box 20, Folder 7)
    - Publication Review Committee (Department of Corrections), 2006. (Box 20, Folder 8)
    - Regional Collaboration Project, 2008-2009. (Box 20, Folder 9)
    - Revenue Data, 2006-2007. (Box 20, Folder 10)
    - Revenue Data, 2008-2009. (Box 20, Folder 11)
    - Rights of Virginians with Disabilities, Department for the, 2001-2002. (Box 20, Folder 12)
    - Riverside Regional Jail, 2002. (Box 20, Folder 13)
    - Science and Crime Prevention: Providing the Foundation for Change, 24-25 April 2006. (Box 20, Folder 14)
    - Secure Commonwealth Panel, 2007. (Box 22b, Folder 9)
    - Secure Commonwealth Initiative Accomplishments, 4 January 2006. (Box 22b, Folder 10)
    - Secure Commonwealth Panel, 2006-2007. (Box 20, Folder 15)
    - Secure Commonwealth Panel, 2002-2004. (Box 20, Folder 16)
    - Senator Howell Visit, 2005. (Box 20, Folder 17)
    - September 11th Anniversary, 2006. (Box 20, Folder 18)
    - Sex Offender Registry Laws, 2005. (Box 20, Folder 19)
    - Sex Offender Registry Laws, 2005. (Box 20, Folder 20)
    - Sexual Violence, Governor's Commission on, 2007. (Box 20, Folder 21)
    - Sexually Violent Predator Referrals, Commitments, and Bed Utilization Forecast (FY2010-FY2015), 2009. (Box 20, Folder 22)
    - "Sight and Sound" (DOC/DJJ), 2005. (Box 20, Folder 23)
    - Speeches and Speaking Engagements, 2005-2006. (Box 20, Folder 24)
    - Speeches and Speaking Engagements, 2006. (Box 20, Folder 25)
    - Speeches and Speaking Engagements, 2007. (Box 20, Folder 26)
    - SPS/OCP Exercise, 2005-2006. (Box 20, Folder 27)
    - Stakeholder Summit, 2007-2009. (Box 20, Folder 28)
    - Auditor of Public Accounts, Interim Review of STARS Project, 2008-2009. (Box 20, Folder 29)
    - State Incentive Grant Advisory Council, 2005. (Box 20, Folder 30)
    - State Police Salaries, 2003. (Box 20, Folder 31)
    - Statewide Interdepartmental Radio System, 2006; 2009. (Box 21, Folder 1)
    - Statewide Community Based Corrections System, 2004. (Box 21, Folder 2)
    - Statewide Financial Management, 2002. (Box 21, Folder 3)
    - Statewide Financial Management, 2002. (Box 21, Folder 4)
    - Statewide Financial Management, 2003. (Box 21, Folder 5)
    - Statewide Financial Management, 2003. (Box 21, Folder 6)
    - Statewide Financial Management, 2004-2005. (Box 21, Folder 7)
    - Statewide Financial Management, 2008. (Box 21, Folder 8)
    - Strategic Planning, 2005. (Box 21, Folder 9)
    - Strategic Planning (HB 2097 Group), 2004-2005. (Box 21, Folder 10)
    - Strategic Planning (HB 2097 Group), 2004-2005. (Box 21, Folder 11)
    - Streamlining/Restructuring Ideas, 2002. (Box 21, Folder 12)
    - Studies, Reports and Evaluations, 2002. (Box 21, Folder 13)
    - Subpoena in Chancery Issued, 2002; 2006. (Box 21, Folder 14)
    - Substance Abuse Prevention, Governor's Office for (GOSAP), 2005-2007. (Box 21, Folder 15)
    - Substance Abuse Prevention, Governor's Office for (GOSAP), 2007. (Box 21, Folder 16)
    - Substance Abuse Services Council, 2005-2007. (Box 21, Folder 17)
    - SWAM Plans, 2009. (Box 21, Folder 18)
    - Swine Flu, 2009. (Box 21, Folder 19)
    - Texas Trip, 2007. (Box 21, Folder 20)
    - 'Town Pickett' Emergency Sheltering and Disaster Assistance Operation: Virginia's Response to Hurricanes Katrina and Rita, 21 December 2005. (Box 21, Folder 21)
    - Uniform Mental Health Screenings, undated. (Box 21, Folder 22)
    - VaLORS, 2005. (Box 21, Folder 23)
    - Vendor Consultants, 2002. (Box 21, Folder 24)
    - Victims Services Background Legislation, 2008-2009. (Box 21, Folder 25)
    - Violent Crime Rates (2004), 2005. (Box 21, Folder 26)
    - Virginia Administrative Support Association, 2003. (Box 21, Folder 27)
    - Virginia 21, April 2008. (Box b22b, Folder 11)
    - Virginia Board for People with Disabilities, Biennial Assessment of the Disability Services System in Virginia, April 2008. (Box 22c, Folder 1)
    - Virginia CARES, 2002. (Box 21, Folder 28)
    - Virginia Citizen-Soldier Support Council, 2006. (Box 21, Folder 29)
    - Virginia Commonwealth University Contract, 2006. (Box 21, Folder 30)
    - Virginia Electric Utility Restructuring Act: A Work in Progress, 24 September 2002. (Box 21, Folder 31)
    - Virginia Liaison Office, 2006. (Box 21, Folder 32)
    - Virginia Military Advisory Council, 2002. (Box 21, Folder 33)
    - Virginia Performs, State Agency Performance Measures, 23 August 2007. (Box 21, Folder 34)
    - Virginia Public Safety: A Resource Guide for Localities, 2007. (Box 21, Folder 35)
    - Virginia Radiological Emergency Response Plan, 2008. (Box 21, Folder 36)
    - Virginia Review, 2006. (Box 21, Folder 37)
    - Virginia Rules Program MOU, 2009. (Box 21, Folder 38)
    - Virginia Sheriffs' Association Conference, 2007. (Box 21, Folder 39)
    - Virginia Tech, 2007. (Box 21, Folder 40)
    - Virginia Tech - Offers of Assistance, 2007. (Box 21, Folder 41)
    - Virginia's Share of Federal Funds, 2002. (Box 22, Folder 1)
    - Vision Statement, undated. (Box 22, Folder 2)
    - VITA/IT, 2003-2004. (Box 22, Folder 3)
    - VITA/IT, 2007. (Box 22, Folder 4)
    - VITA/IT: Certification of Public Safety Agency IT Strategic Plan Data, 2003. (Box 22c, Folder 2)
    - VITA/IT: Public Safety Agency IT Strategic Plans, 2004. (Box 22c, Folder 3)
    - VITA/IT: Public Safety Agency Investment Project Proposals, 2003. (Box 22c, Folder 4)
    - VITA/Information Technology Investment Board, Recommended Technology Investment Projects Report for the 2006-2008 Budget Biennium, 1 September 2005. (Box 22, Folder 5)
    - Virginia Port Authority, January 2008. (Box 22c, Folder 5)
    - Virginia Supreme Court, So You're 18: A Handbook on your Legal Rights and Responsibilities, undated. (Box 22c, Folder 6)
    - Website, 2007. (Box 22, Folder 6)
    - Wilder Commission, 2002. (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - Series II. Correspondence and Supporting Documentation - Office of the Secretary, Subseries C. Records of Deputy Secretary Barry Green, 1998-2005., Extent: 3.0 cu. ft. (boxes 23-25)
    This subseries is housed in 3 boxes and is arranged alphabetically by agency or subject. It contains correspondence and subject files kept by Deputy Secretary of Public Safety Barry Green during the administration of Governor Mark R. Warner (2002-2006). This series contains correspondence, email printouts, budget documents, news articles, reports and studies, memorandums, decision briefs, executive orders, and legislation.
    - Agency Reports and Studies, 2004-2005. (Box 23, Folder 1)
    - Agency Reports and Studies, 2005. (Box 23, Folder 2)
    - Agency Reports and Studies, 2005. (Box 23, Folder 3)
    - Agency Reports and Studies, 2005. (Box 23, Folder 4)
    - Alcoholic Beverage Control, 2002. (Box 23, Folder 5)
    - Alcoholic Beverage Control, 2002. (Box 23, Folder 6)
    - Alcoholic Beverage Control, 2003. (Box 23, Folder 7)
    - Alcoholic Beverage Control, 2003. (Box 23, Folder 8)
    - Alcoholic Beverage Control, 2003. (Box 23, Folder 9)
    - Alcoholic Beverage Control, 2003-2004. (Box 23, Folder 10)
    - Alcoholic Beverage Control, 2004. (Box 23, Folder 11)
    - Alcoholic Beverage Control, 2004. (Box 23, Folder 12)
    - Correspondence with Secretary John Marshall, 2002-2004. (Box 23, Folder 13)
    - Corrections, Department of, 2002. (Box 23, Folder 14)
    - Corrections, Department of, 2002. (Box 23, Folder 15)
    - Corrections, Department of, 2003. (Box 23, Folder 16)
    - Corrections, Department of, 2003. (Box 23, Folder 17)
    - Corrections, Department of, 2004. (Box 23, Folder 18)
    - Corrections, Department of, 2004. (Box 23, Folder 19)
    - Corrections, Department of, 2004. (Box 23, Folder 20)
    - Corrections, Department of, 2005. (Box 23, Folder 21)
    - Corrections Investigations, 2002. (Box 23, Folder 22)
    - Corrections Investigations, 2002. (Box 23, Folder 23)
    - Criminal Justice Services, Department of, 2002. (Box 23, Folder 24)
    - Criminal Justice Services, Department of - Staffing Request (FY2005), 2004. (Box 24, Folder 1)
    - Diversity Fair, 2005. (Box 24, Folder 2)
    - Executive Orders, 2002. (Box 24, Folder 3)
    - Inmate Forecasting, 2002. (Box 24, Folder 4)
    - Inmate Forecasting, 2002. (Box 24, Folder 5)
    - Inmate Forecasting, 2003. (Box 24, Folder 6)
    - Inmate Forecasting, 2003. (Box 24, Folder 7)
    - Inmate Forecasting, 2004. (Box 24, Folder 8)
    - Inmate Forecasting, 2005. (Box 24, Folder 9)
    - Inmate Mail, 2002. (Box 24, Folder 10)
    - Juvenile Justice, Department of, 2002. (Box 24, Folder 11)
    - Juvenile Justice, Department of, 2002. (Box 24, Folder 12)
    - Juvenile Justice, Department of, 2003. (Box 24, Folder 13)
    - Juvenile Justice, Department of, 2004. (Box 24, Folder 14)
    - Juvenile Justice, Department of - Data Resource Guide, 2003. (Box 24, Folder 15)
    - Juvenile Correctional Center Utilization Report, 2004. (Box 24, Folder 16)
    - Lawrenceville Correctional Center Contract, 2003. (Box 24, Folder 17)
    - Lawrenceville Correctional Center Contract, 2003-2004. (Box 24, Folder 18)
    - NAACP, 2002-2003. (Box 24, Folder 19)
    - Offender Population Forecasts, 1998; 2001. (Box 24, Folder 20)
    - Offender Population Forecasts, 2002-2003. (Box 24, Folder 21)
    - Offender Population Forecasts, 2004-2005. (Box 25, Folder 1)
    - Offender Population Forecasts, 1998-2000. (Box 25, Folder 2)
    - Parole Board, 2002. (Box 25, Folder 3)
    - Parole Board, 2003. (Box 25, Folder 4)
    - Sexually Violent Predators, 2002-2003. (Box 25, Folder 5)
    - Sexually Violent Predators, 2002-2003. (Box 25, Folder 6)
    - Sexually Violent Predators, 2002-2003. (Box 25, Folder 7)
    - Sexually Violent Predators, 2002-2003. (Box 25, Folder 8)
    - Sexually Violent Predators, 2003. (Box 25, Folder 9)
    - Sexually Violent Predators, 2003. (Box 25, Folder 10)
    - Sexually Violent Predators, 2003. (Box 25, Folder 11)
    - Sexually Violent Predators, 2003. (Box 25, Folder 12)
    - Sexually Violent Predators, 2003-2004. (Box 25, Folder 13)
    - SJR 97 (Treatment for Offenders), 2002-2003. (Box 25, Folder 14)
    - SJR 97 (Treatment for Offenders), 2002-2003. (Box 25, Folder 15)
    - SJR 97 (Treatment for Offenders), 2002-2003. (Box 25, Folder 16)
    - Staunton Correctional Center, 2002. (Box 25, Folder 17)
    - Staunton Correctional Center, 2002-2003. (Box 25, Folder 18)
    - Statewide Agencies Radio System (STARS), 2002. (Box 25, Folder 19)
    - Statewide Agencies Radio System (STARS), 2002-2005. (Box 25, Folder 20)
    - Substance Abuse Prevention, Governor's Office of, 2002. (Box 25, Folder 21)
  - Series II. Correspondence and Supporting Documentation - Office of the Secretary, Subseries D. Records of Assistant Secretary Dawn Smith, 2002-2008., Extent: 3.0 cu. ft. (boxes 26-28)
    This subseries is housed in three boxes and is arranged alphabetically by agency or subject. It contains correspondence and subject files kept by Assistant Secretary of Public Safety Dawn Smith during the administrations of Governor Mark R. Warner (2002-2006) and Governor Timothy M. Kaine (2006-2010). This series contains correspondence, email printouts, budget documents, news articles, reports and studies, memorandums, decision briefs, executive orders, and legislation. The bulk of the subseries contains constituent correspondence related to the possible location of a prison in Grayson County and the Citizen-Soldier initiative. Also include are records related to minority procurement.
    - Alcoholic Beverage Control, Dept. of, undated. (Box 26, Folder 1)
    - Biased Policing Panel, 2003. (Box 26, Folder 2)
    - Budget Amendments, 2006 Special Session, 2006. (Box 26, Folder 2a)
    - Civil Commitment Procedures, 2003. (Box 26, Folder 3)
    - Civil Commitment Procedures, 2003-2004. (Box 26, Folder 4)
    - Civil Commitment Procedures Work Group, 2003-2004. (Box 26, Folder 5)
    - Fire Programs, Dept. of, 2006. (Box 26, Folder 6)
    - Governor's Preventing Crime in Minority Communities Task Force, 2003-2004. (Box 26, Folder 7)
    - Governor's Preventing Crime in Minority Communities Task Force, 2003-2004. (Box 26, Folder 8)
    - Governor's Preventing Crime in Minority Communities Task Force, 2005. (Box 26, Folder 9)
    - Grayson County Prison Site, 2006. (Box 26, Folder 10)
    - Grayson County Prison Correspondence, Batch 1 (8 January 2007)
      - Constituent Correspondence, A-H, 2006-2007. (Box 26, Folder 11)
      - Constituent Correspondence, I-O, 2006-2007. (Box 26, Folder 12)
      - Constituent Correspondence, P-Y, 2006-2007. (Box 26, Folder 13)
    - Grayson County Prison Correspondence, Batch 2 - Out of State (8 January 2007)
      - Constituent Correspondence, A-G, 2006-2007. (Box 26, Folder 14)
      - Constituent Correspondence, H-M, 2006-2007. (Box 26, Folder 15)
      - Constituent Correspondence, Mc-Y, 2006-2007. (Box 26, Folder 16)
    - Grayson County Prison Correspondence, Batch 3 - In-State and Out of State (January to March 2007)
      - Constituent Correspondence, A-O, 2007. (Box 26, Folder 17)
      - Constituent Correspondence, P-W, 2007. (Box 26, Folder 18)
      - Post Cards, Public Information Meeting, 2007. (Box 26, Folder 19)
    - Grayson County Prison Correspondence, Batch 4 - (December 2006 to March 2007)
      - Constituent Correspondence, A-K, 2006-2007. (Box 26, Folder 20)
      - Constituent Correspondence, L-S, 2006-2007. (Box 26, Folder 21)
      - Constituent Correspondence, T, 2007. (Box 26, Folder 22)
      - Constituent Correspondence, U-Y, 2006-2007. (Box 26, Folder 23)
      - Constituent Correspondence forwarded from the Dept. of Conservation and Recreation, 2006-2007. (Box 26, Folder 24)
      - Petition Opposing Prison, undated. (Box 26, Folder 25)
    - Juvenile Justice, Dept. of, 2006. (Box 27, Folder 1)
    - Public Safety Supplier Diversity Fair, 2005. (Box 27, Folder 2)
    - Public Safety Supplier Diversity Fair, 2005. (Box 27, Folder 3)
    - Public Safety Supplier Diversity Fair I, 2006. (Box 27, Folder 4)
    - Public Safety Supplier Diversity Fair II, 2006. (Box 27, Folder 5)
    - Public Safety Supplier Diversity Fair II, 2006. (Box 27, Folder 6)
    - Public Safety Supplier Diversity Fair III, 2007. (Box 27, Folder 7)
    - Public Safety Supplier Diversity Fair III, 2007. (Box 27, Folder 8)
    - Public Safety Supplier Diversity Fair IV, 2007. (Box 27, Folder 9)
    - Small, Women-owned, and Minority-owned Business (SWAM), 2004. (Box 27, Folder 10)
    - Small, Women-owned, and Minority-owned Business (SWAM), 2004. (Box 27, Folder 11)
    - Small, Women-owned, and Minority-owned Business (SWAM), 2004-2005. (Box 27, Folder 12)
    - Small, Women-owned, and Minority-owned Business (SWAM), 2006. (Box 27, Folder 13)
    - Small, Women-owned, and Minority-owned Business (SWAM) Monthly Reports, 2005-2006. (Box 27, Folder 14)
    - Small, Women-owned, and Minority-owned Business (SWAM) Perspective (videotape), undated. (Box 27, Folder 15)
    - Urban Policy Task Force, 2006. (Box 27, Folder 16)
    - Urban Policy Task Force, 2006-2007. (Box 27, Folder 17)
    - Virginia Citizen-Soldier Support Council
      - Virginia Citizen-Soldier Support Council Meeting, 26 June 2003. (Box 27, Folder 18)
      - Virginia Citizen-Soldier Support Council Meeting, 3 November 2003. (Box 27, Folder 18)
      - Virginia Citizen-Soldier Support Council Meeting, 12 May 2004. (Box 27, Folder 18)
      - Local and State Government Committee of the Citizen-Soldier Support Council, September 2004 to December 2004. (Box 27, Folder 19)
      - Virginia Citizen Soldier-Support Council Meeting, 6 October 2004. (Box 27, Folder 20)
      - Overview of Governor Warner's Virginia Citizen-Soldier Support Council, 20 January 2005. (Box 27, Folder 21)
      - Virginia Citizen-Soldier Support Council Meeting, 19 April 2005. (Box 27, Folder 21)
      - Virginia Citizen-Soldier Support Council Meeting, 14 July 2005. (Box 27, Folder 21)
      - Virginia Citizen-Soldier Support Council Meeting, 24 August 2005. (Box 27, Folder 22)
      - Virginia Citizen-Soldier Support Council Meeting, 27 October 2005. (Box 27, Folder 23)
      - Virginia Citizen-Soldier Support Council Meeting, 8 December 2005. (Box 27, Folder 23)
      - Virginia Citizen-Soldier Support Council Meeting, 13 December 2005. (Box 27, Folder 23)
      - Virginia Citizen-Soldier Support Council Meeting Follow-up, 13 December 2005-April 2006. (Box 27, Folder 24)
      - Virginia Citizen-Soldier Support Council Meeting, 19 June 2006. (Box 27, Folder 25)
      - Virginia Citizen-Soldier Support Council, Legislative and Event Planning Meeting, 21 July 2006. (Box 28, Folder 1)
      - Virginia Citizen-Soldier Support Council, Military Family Appreciation and Information Fair, 4 August 2006. (Box 28, Folder 2)
      - Virginia Citizen-Soldier Support Council Meeting, 29 August 2006. (Box 28, Folder 2)
      - Virginia Citizen-Soldier Support Council Meeting, 13 December 2006. (Box 28, Folder 3)